vaporshark.com 2014-11-29

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Vapor Shark understands that your privacy is important, especially when providing sensitive, personal information on the internet. This Notice will govern our Privacy Policy applies to all users of this website, whether or not a transaction of any kind is conducted during each browser session.

 **Your Personal Information:**  
Your information will never be shared with any third party. When you create a user account on-line or communicate with us via e-mail, letter, fax, or phone, we receive and store the information that you have provided. This information is basic, including: name, address, phone, fax and cell phone numbers, e-mail address and business information (if applicable). We use this information for purposes such as responding to your requests, communicating with you, and customizing future shopping for you. Cookies: We use cookies to obtain a variety of information which provides us details about what product and information interest our visitors view the most. Cookies can also be used to protect your information. If you wish to disable our cookie from obtaining this information, you can do this on your browser or seek programs that will allow you to visit our site anonymously without losing most of the site's functionality.

**  
Does Vaporshark.com Share the Information it Receives?  
** Under no circumstances will we ever give away or sell your personal information to anyone else for any reason whatsoever. Any information we gain through our use of community polls, surveys, cookies, session tracking or anything else, is used internally and for the sole purpose of providing you better service. If you are on our mailing list and you ask us to remove you, we will do so immediately and will not attempt to sell your information. We respect your privacy.

 **  
How Secure is My Information?**  
Your personal information is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to database information. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electric communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering, and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place. We will not be liable for any such occurrences. You will find that almost all Internet e-commerce providers make this same claim, especially if they establish privacy policies such as this one.  
 ****

 **Are Children Allowed to Use Vapor Shark Electronic Cigarettes?**

 **  
**No. Our products are sold only to adult smokers, 18 years or older. Vapor Shark does not intentionally collect or solicit personal information from or about children or anyone under the age of 18. If we discover we have received any information from an individual under the age of 18 and in violation of this Policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Vapor Shark has any information from or about anyone under the age of 18, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will do our best to resolve it.  
 **

Privacy Policy Changes

** **  
**Because our business changes constantly, our Privacy Policy and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our Notices and Conditions, unless you have instructed us not to. You should check our Web Site frequently to view recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of collected customer information without the consent of affected customers. **  
**
